KRISTIAN WORTHY

A college graduate from the University of North Carolina Wilmington with a bachelor's degree in Communication Studies and a minor in Digital Arts, with a focus in Integrated Marketing Communication (IMC). Goal-oriented marketing analyst with hands-on experience in the fields of Digital Marketing and Event marketing for almost a year. Acquiring versatile skillsets in different marketing fields that will help me adapt to changing environments that companies experience.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Event Marketing
- Digital Marketing
- User Acceptance Testing (UAT)
- Web Quality Assurance

- Basic HTML/CSS/JavaScript knowledge
- Copy Editing
- Graphic Design
- Typography

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ArmorBlue Consulting, Charlotte, NC

Digital Marketing Analyst

08/2019 - Present

Key Accomplishments:

- Coordinated and worked with web engineers and marketing partners on a large project, which required significant analyst skills to tag large amounts of content for the website.
- Created, organized and managed a promo checklist of requirements for web producers and digital marketing partners, so that new promos and campaign launches could be executed smoothly to reduce errors.
- Helped the web marketing team conduct a web audit of legal language on the website that would satisfy legal requirements to ensure that various QuickBooks websites remain in compliance.

ArmorBlue Consulting, Charlotte, NC

Event Marketing

08/2019 - Present

Key Accomplishments

• Helped manage the registration desk and train local staff on the registration process for FireEye conferences in the Cyber Security field

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATES

Bachelor of Arts: University of North Carolina Wilmington, Wilmington, NC	08/2016 - 05/2019
Inbound Marketing Certificate: HubSpot Academy	02/2020 - 03/2022
HubSpot Marketing Software Certificate: HubSpot Academy	02/2020 - 02/2021
Google Analytics for Beginners: Google Analytics	03/2020 - 03/2023

RECOGNITION & ACHIEVEMENTS

• Co-President of the Communication Honor Society, Lambda Pi Eta (LPH)

08/2018 - 05/2019

- Deans list of the College of Arts & Sciences 2019
- Deans list at Central Piedmont Community College 2016